<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <origin/>
                <pubdate>20200305</pubdate>
                <title>TCBuildings</title>
                <onlink>https://services.arcgis.com/oJbAAWNInLrxvF0A/arcgis/rest/services/TCBuildings/FeatureServer</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>The data represents generalized building footprints for Tompkins County as of March 5, 2020. Data has been updated for recently built areas with 2018 Ortho Photography or approximated from paper surveys for buildings currently under construction.</abstract>
            <purpose>Tompkins County Building Footprints as of March 5, 2020</purpose>
            <supplinf>This data set is intended for use as a general reference map layer for GIS maps and applications.</supplinf>
        </descript>
        <timeperd>
            <timeinfo>
                <rngdates>
                    <begdate>20051005</begdate>
                    <enddate>20200305</enddate>
                </rngdates>
            </timeinfo>
            <current>Dates for which dataset is valid</current>
        </timeperd>
        <status>
            <progress>In work</progress>
            <update>Monthly</update>
        </status>
        <spdom>
            <bounding>
                <westbc>-76.7966</westbc>
                <eastbc>-76.2267</eastbc>
                <northbc>42.6865</northbc>
                <southbc>42.2682</southbc>
            </bounding>
        </spdom>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>buildings</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>Access: Open to the public.Disclaimer: The information provided within these applications are for your convenience, and the data provided herein is for general reference only. These products are for informational purposes and may not have been prepared for or be suitable for legal, engineering, or surveying purposes. It does not represent an on-the-ground survey and represents only the approximate relative location of property boundaries. Verifying the accuracy of all information provided here is the responsibility of the user. Maps may be printed for your convenience, with the understanding that they will be used for general reference only, without any claims of completeness or accuracy. Please do not redistribute data to a third party without permission from Tompkins County GIS.</useconst>
        <ptcontac>
            <cntinfo>
                <cntorgp>
                    <cntorg>Tompkins County Department of Information Technology: GIS Division</cntorg>
                    <cntper>Cattyann Campbell</cntper>
                </cntorgp>
                <cntpos>GIS Administrator</cntpos>
                <cntaddr>
                    <addrtype>physical</addrtype>
                    <address>128 E Buffalo St</address>
                    <city>Ithaca</city>
                    <state>NY</state>
                    <postal>14850</postal>
                    <country>US</country>
                </cntaddr>
                <cntvoice>607-274-5418</cntvoice>
                <cntemail>gis@tompkins-co.org</cntemail>
                <hours>8:30 AM  to 4:30 PM</hours>
                <cntinst>Email preferred</cntinst>
            </cntinfo>
        </ptcontac>
        <datacred>Tompkins County GIS Division, Tompkins County Planning Department, Tompkins County Department of Assessment</datacred>
        <native>Hitachi Feature Extraction Process, Automated feature extraction process from Tyler Technologies based on 2018 imagery, Head up digitizing in ArcMap.</native>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20200305</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <cntorgp>
                    <cntorg>Tompkins County Department of Information Technology: GIS Division</cntorg>
                    <cntper>Cattyann Campbell</cntper>
                </cntorgp>
                <cntpos>GIS Administrator</cntpos>
                <cntaddr>
                    <addrtype>physical</addrtype>
                    <address>128 E Buffalo St</address>
                    <city>Ithaca</city>
                    <state>NY</state>
                    <postal>14850</postal>
                    <country>US</country>
                </cntaddr>
                <cntvoice>607-274-5418</cntvoice>
                <cntemail>gis@tompkins-co.org</cntemail>
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
